Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Files
  - Project Files
    - Barnsdall Park - Landscaping
      - Specifications & agreements - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Planting - general & grading specifications - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Client correspondence - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Road work - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Maintenance - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Barnsdall, Aline - Children's outdoor theatre
      - General, Project No. 67 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Bartfield - Residence
      - Desk folder, Project No. 258 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Bassett, Dorothy - Landscaping
      - General, Project No. 52 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bassett, J.B. & Dorothy - Cascades Club
      - General, Project No. 83 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Baxter, Anne - Pool remodel
      - General (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Baxter, Anne - Residence remodel
      - General, Project No. 167 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Baxter, Mr. & Mrs. Kenneth - Residence
      - Correspondence, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Client notes & cuts (1 of 2), Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Client notes & cuts (2 of 2), Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Land surveys, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Estimates & various lists, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Estimates - quantity surveys, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Estimates, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Specifications, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Outline specifications, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Contractors, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Sub-contractors, Project No. 172 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Beachy, Walter - Residence & farm group projects
      - General, Project No. 109 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Behn, Harry - Residence
      - unspecified, Project No. 49 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Bellenson, Leonard - Residence
      - Engineering calculations (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Estimates (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Sub - contractors bids (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - State architectural complaint file (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Land survey (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Client - notes & cuts (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - heating / air conditioning (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - concrete (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - Mill work, doors, windows (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - sheet metal work (Box 90, Folder 21)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - Lathing & plastering (Box 90, Folder 22)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - cabinet work (Box 90, Folder 23)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - electrical work (Box 90, Folder 24)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - General file (Box 90, Folder 25)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - builder's control (Box 90, Folder 26)
      - Contractor's bids (Box 90, Folder 27)
      - Landscaping (Box 90, Folder 28)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - grading (Box 90, Folder 29)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - superintendence & framing (Box 90, Folder 30)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - tile (Box 90, Folder 31)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - hardware & bathroom accessories (Box 90, Folder 32)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - masonry (Box 90, Folder 33)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - glass (Box 90, Folder 34)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - plumbing (Box 90, Folder 35)
      - Sub-contractor contracts - painting (Box 90, Folder 36)
      - Builder's control form (Box 90, Folder 37)
      - Release slips (Box 90, Folder 38)
      - Vouchers (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 39)
      - Vouchers (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 40)
      - Vouchers - unpaid (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Construction - applications (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Construction - job notes (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Weatherproof Products Inc. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Benjamin, L.B. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 154 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Blalock, Francis - Apartments
      - Client - notes & cuts, Project No. 191 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 191 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - Estimates - cost & recapitulation, Project No. 191 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - General specifications, Project No. 191 (Box 57, Folder 32)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 191 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Bollman, Henry - Residence
      - General, Project No. 10 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Bothwell, Mr. & Mrs. Murray - Nurse Association
      - Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Bothwell, Mr. & Mrs. Murray - Residence
      - Specifications, Project No. 157A (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Contractor's payments, Project No. 157A (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Estimates & survey notes, Project No. 157A (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Bowler, John - Residence
      - General (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Bowler, John - Screen & furniture
      - Desk folder (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Desk folder (2 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Draperies & furniture (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Interior decoration (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Construction (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Brower, Mr. & Mrs. Otto - Residence
      - General, Project No. 101 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Brower, Ms. Pern - Residence
      - General, Project No. 155 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Butterworth, Charles - Residence
      - General, Project No. 106 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - California Art Club - Waterproofing club building
      - 1934 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - California Housing Authority
      - Newsletters & clippings (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Cardenas, Francisco - Garden
      - General, Project No. 153 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Carr, Harry & Alice - Residence
      - (1 of 2), Project No. 22 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - (2 of 2), Project No. 22 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Carroll, Veda - Residence
      - Contracts (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Childs, Robert - House at Institute
      - General, Project No. 248 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Church of New Jerusalem - Church & apartment
      - Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Notes & cuts (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Agreements & certificates (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Client file (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Colbert, Claudette - Residence
      - General, Project No. 91 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Connell, Will - Residence
      - Correspondence, Project No. 40 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Bills, Project No. 40 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Conselman, Will - Residence
      - General, Project No. 39 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Crosby, Floyd - Residence
      - General, Project No. 148 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Crosby, William & Marilyn - Residence remodel
      - Manufacturer's brochure (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Architect - billings (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Engineering calculations (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Specifications (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Specifications ( 2 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Owner / Contractor agreement (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Day, Richard - Residence
      - Bids, Project No. 57 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Architect's statements, Project No. 57 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Papers on "original" job, Project No. 51 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - "Original" job - addition, Project No. 51 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Specifications, Project No. 51 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 51 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - De Jonghe, Daniel - Residence
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Rebuttal Environmental Impact Study Concerning Former Air Force Laboratory, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Journal, Nov. 1959 - Nov. 1961, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Voided contract data, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Construction - contractors, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Construction - bids, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Construction - applications, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Construction - contractors' & owner's agreement, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Construction - certificates, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Construction - Frank J. Ligar vouchers, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Construction - grading, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Construction - job progress reports, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Construction - Frank J. Ligar correspondence, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Land survey, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Architect's agreement, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Lumber list, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - Engineering estimate, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - Deposition, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - De Jonghe journal notes used at arbitration, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Frank Ligar construction file, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - Supervision journal, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Arbitration data, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - Legal, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - Quantity estimates, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 38)
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 39)
      - Bids & notes, Project No. 195 (Box 58, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence - Van Tassel (1 of 2), Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - Van Tassel (2 of 2), Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Owner's completion account, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Grading permit, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence & data, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Grading contracts, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Electrical contracts, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Plumbing specifications & data, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Various data, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Heating, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Agreements, liens, photographs, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Specifications, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - General specifications - obsolete data, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Sub-contractors - specifications, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Job notes, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Construction report, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Bonding company claims, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Letters - Van Tassel, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Grading permit & correspondence, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Yellow notes, Project No. 195 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Dean, W.E. - Road & carport
      - General, Project No. 175 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Degener, Armin - Residence
      - General (1 of 2), Project No. 123 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - General (2 of 2), Project No. 123 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - General, Project No. 135 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Dell, George M. - Residence
      - Supervisor's journal, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Client correspondence & notes, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Land survey, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - Estimates - quantity survey, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Estimates - engineering, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - Construction, Project No. 233 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Dodd, W.J. - Landscaping
      - General, Project No. 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Dorland, Allen - Residence
      - Specifications, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Residence addition from 1957, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Land survey, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Architect's agreements, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Estimates - quantity survey, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Estimates - engineering data, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - General specifications, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Construction contract, Project No. 189 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Duffil, Alma Norton - Residence
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 185 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Dunham, Lowell - Residence
      - General (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Eddy, Nelson - Studio
      - Estimate, Project No. 130 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Edens, Roger - Residence remodel
      - General, Project No. 100 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, Project No. 100 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Specifications, Project No. 100 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - El Cerrito Church - Chapel
      - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Client - photos (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Client - sub-division data (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Client notes (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Land survey (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Architect's agreements (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Architect's studies (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Model - billing (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Architect - travel (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Estimates (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Construction (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Supervision journal (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Trips (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Erickson family - Family memorial
      - General, Project No. 316 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Erickson family - Holiday service station
      - General, Project No. 316 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Erickson, Alfred - Residence
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Land survey, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Estimates, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Specifications, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Erickson, Alfred & Arthur - Residences
      - Lily pond data, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Catalogues, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Construction, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Brass trim, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Slides & photographs, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Erickson, Arthur - Residence
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Client notes, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Land survey, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Estimates, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Bids, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Specifications, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 202 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Evans, Warwick - Residence
      - General, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Bids & contracts, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence & legal, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Specifications, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Bids, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Architect's agreements & statements, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Repair bills & final statements, Project No. 99 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Fairmont Hotel - Tower & remodel
      - General, Project No. 147 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Farrell, John J. - Residence
      - unspecified, Project No. 36 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Fink, David - Residence
      - Client - notes & cuts, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Architect's certificates & agreements, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Estimates, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Client's correspondence, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 197 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - First Christian Church - Church - first phase
      - Second phase - construction (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - Cost estimates (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - Electrical engineers (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - Mechanical engineers (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - Supervision journal (Box 87, Folder 28)
      - Structural engineering (Box 87, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 31)
      - Plan schedule & notes (Box 87, Folder 32)
      - Client - publicity (Box 87, Folder 33)
      - Client - notes (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Client - notes (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Client - historical background & stained glass window literature (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Preliminary data (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Photos (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Church publications (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Church publications (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Land survey (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Soils engineering (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Soils engineering (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Architect' studies (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Engineering contracts (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Architect - notes (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Engineering estimates & calculations (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - Specifications (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - Specifications - masters (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - Specifications - general notes (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - Specifications - general notes (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - Pamphlets (Box 88, Folder 21)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Church furniture (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Construction - bids (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Contracts & proposals (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Construction - material bills (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Shop drawings & specifications (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Seating arrangement & choir area (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Construction - model data (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Construction - testing materials (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Applications (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Construction - job notes (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Zoning data (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Variance application (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Zoning notes (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - Specifications (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Specifications (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Specifications (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - First Christian Church - Church
      - Brochure notes & mockup (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Brochure (1 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Brochure (2 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Architect's statements (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Client's pamphlets & literature (1 of 3) (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Client's pamphlets & literature (2 of 3) (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Client's pamphlets & literature (3 of 3) (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Forsch, Charles - Residence
      - General, Project No. 149 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Four Square Housing
      - General, Project No. 119 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Furthman, Jules - Residence
      - General, Project No. 70 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Gainsburg, Mr. & Mrs. Emanuel - Residence, garage & landscaping
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 169 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 169 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 169 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Literature, Project No. 169 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Land surveys, Project No. 169 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      - Agreements, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Estimates, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Specifications, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Contractors, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Sub-contractors, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Bids, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Job notes, Project No. 169 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gilkerson, J.K. - Landscaping
      - unspecified, Project No. 21 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Good Shephard Community Church - Basement
      - Photographs (Box 66, Folder 29)
      - Client data (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Good Shephard Community Church - Chapel
      - Construction - contractor / owner agreements (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - 10th trip job notes (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Construction - contractor Lindstrom - certificates (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Construction - Lindstrom - certificate data (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Construction - lists & letters (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Construction - final statement (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Construction - check list (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Construction - painting (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Construction - letters (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Construction - vouchers (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Construction - electrical (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Construction - Lindstrom (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Construction - light fixtures (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Construction - plastic panels (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Construction - Hufcor door (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Good Shepherd Community Church - Church
      - Construction - bids (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Construction - contractors (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Planting & roof problems (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Construction - contractors (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Desk folder (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Actual Specifying Engineer, vol. 1., no. 1 (Sept. 1958) (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Client correspondence (1 of 4) (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Client correspondence (2 of 4) (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Client correspondence (3 of 4) (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Client correspondence (4 of 4) (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Richard Nickel - photographer (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence - Fill & rezoning (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - Dedication service, May 1961 (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - Client notes & cuts (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - Outline of preliminary proposals (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - Literature (Box 66, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence - Alice Memmoth (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Furniture, robe colors, painting & decorating (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Land survey (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Architect's agreements and certificates (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Architect - trip billings (Box 67, Folder 5)